bangalore5.com 2014-06-25

# bangalore5, 2bhk apartment for sale in Bangalore, 2bhk apartment in Bangalore, Bangalore property

## Privacy Policy (Bangalore5.com)

The Privacy policy is subject to the terms of the Site Policy of Bangalore5.com. This policy is effective from the date and time a user registers with Bangalore5.com by filling up the Registration form and accepting the terms and conditions laid out in the Site Policy. 

In order to provide a personalized browsing experience, Bangalore5.com may collect personal information such as Name, age, sex, Email address etc from you. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your requirement. 

To extend this personalized experience Bangalore5.com may track the IP address of a user's computer and save certain information on your system in the form of cookies. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings of your browser. 

The personal information provided by the users to Bangalore5.com will not be provided to third parties without previous consent of the user concerned. Information of a general nature may however be revealed to external parties 

Every effort will be made to keep the information provided by users in a safe manner, the information will be displayed on the website will be done so only after obtaining consent from the users. Any user browsing the site generally is not required to disclose his identity or provide any information about him/her; it is only at the time of registration you will be required to furnish the details in the registration form. 

A user always has the option of not providing the information which is not mandatory. You are solely responsible for maintaining confidentiality of the User password and user identification and all activities and transmission performed by the User through his user identification and shall be solely responsible for carrying out any online or off-line transaction involving credit cards / debit cards or such other forms of instruments or documents for making such transactions and BANGALORE PROPERTY 4U assumes no responsibility or liability for their improper use of information relating to such usage of debit cards / credit cards used by the Registered user Off- line / online. 

You agree that BANGALORE5.com may use personal information provided by you to improve its marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site. 

You agree that BANGALORE5.com may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you which, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time. At all times we strive hard to protect your privacy by working as per the rules and regulations of relevant laws in force. 

All BANGALORE5.com websites including Bangalore5.com fully comply with all Indian Laws that are applicable. BANGALORE5.com has always cooperated with all law enforcement inquires. BANGALORE5.com may disclose all or part of your personal details in response to a request from the law enforcement authorities or in a case of bonafide requirement to prevent an imminent breach of the law. 

If you require more information or have any questions regarding this statement, you may write to us : **Contact us :- office@bangalore5.com**
